Guide to the Richard Hell Papers 1944-2003 (Bulk 1969-2003) MSS.140
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Projects
  - Subseries P: CUZ
    - Manuscript, Ameen, Mark, undated (Box 11, Folder 802)
    - Manuscript, Andrews, Bruce, undated (Box 11, Folder 803)
    - Manuscript, Ashbery, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 804)
    - Manuscript, Brodey, Jim, undated (Box 11, Folder 805)
    - Manuscript, Brown, Lee Ann, undated (Box 11, Folder 806)
    - Manuscript, Brown, Lee Ann Hear, Say, undated (Box 11, Folder 807)
    - Manuscript, Burroughs, William, undated (Box 11, Folder 808)
    - Manuscript, Carter, Ellen, undated (Box 12, Folder 809)
    - Manuscript, Cooper, Dennis, Closer, undated (Box 12, Folder 810)
    - Manuscript, Cooper, Dennis, Closer excerpts, undated (Box 12, Folder 811)
    - Manuscript, Cooper, Dennis, interview w/Nick Zedd (tapes), undated (Box 12, Folder 812)
    - Manuscript, Cooper, Dennis, interview w/Nick Zedd, undated (Box 12, Folder 813)
    - Manuscript, DeCapite, Mike, undated (Box 12, Folder 814)
    - Manuscript, Deering, Donald, undated (Box 12, Folder 815)
    - Manuscript, Dubris, Maggie, undated (Box 12, Folder 816)
    - Manuscript, Dubris, Maggie WillieWorld, undated (Box 12, Folder 817)
    - Manuscript, Equi, Elaine, undated (Box 12, Folder 818)
    - Manuscript, Exquisite Corpse, undated (Box 12, Folder 819)
    - Manuscript, Fagin, Larry, undated (Box 12, Folder 820)
    - Manuscript, Godfrey, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 821)
    - Manuscript, Hardin, Terri, undated (Box 12, Folder 822)
    - Manuscript, Hell, Richard collaborations, undated (Box 12, Folder 823)
    - Manuscript, Hell Richard, poems, undated (Box 12, Folder 824)
    - Manuscript, Hell, Richard, editor's notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 825)
    - Manuscript, Hell, Richard interview w/Dennis Cooper, undated (Box 12, Folder 826)
    - Manuscript, Hell, Richard, interview w/ Nick Zedd (tape), undated (Box 12, Folder 827)
    - Manuscript, Hell, Richard, addendum to Zedd interview, undated (Box 12, Folder 828)
    - Manuscript, Highfill, Mitch, undated (Box 12, Folder 829)
    - Manuscript, Johnson, Janice, undated (Box 12, Folder 830)
    - Manuscript, Killian, Kevin, undated (Box 12, Folder 831)
    - Manuscript, Kraut, Rochelle, undated (Box 12, Folder 832)
    - Manuscript, Lyons, Kim, undated (Box 12, Folder 833)
    - Manuscript, Michaels, Abbie, undated (Box 12, Folder 834)
    - Manuscript, Mueller, Cookie, undated (Box 12, Folder 835)
    - Manuscript, Myles, Eileen, undated (Box 12, Folder 836)
    - Manuscript, Myles, Eileen, Feeling Blue, undated (Box 12, Folder 837)
    - Manuscript, Patton, Will, undated (Box 12, Folder 838)
    - Manuscript, Patton, Will, Notebook 1, undated (Box 12, Folder 839)
    - Manuscript, Patton, Will, Notebook 2, undated (Box 12, Folder 840)
    - Manuscript, Rand, William, undated (Box 12, Folder 841)
    - Manuscript, Ricard, Rene, undated (Box 12, Folder 842)
    - Manuscript, Robinson, Elizabeth, undated (Box 12, Folder 843)
    - Manuscript, Russakoff, Molly, undated (Box 12, Folder 844)
    - Manuscript, Sala, Jerome, undated (Box 12, Folder 845)
    - Manuscript, Sparrow, undated (Box 12, Folder 846)
    - Manuscript, Timmons, Suzie, undated (Box 12, Folder 847)
    - Manuscript, Trinidad, David, undated (Box 12, Folder 848)
    - Manuscript, Wojnarowicz, David, undated (Box 12, Folder 849)
    - Manuscript, Yau, John, undated (Box 12, Folder 850)
    - Manuscript, Zedd, Nick, undated (Box 12, Folder 851)
    - Manuscript, Zivancevic, Mina, undated (Box 12, Folder 852)
    - Manuscript, Unidentified, undated (Box 12, Folder 853)
    - Artwork, Nick Zedd, undated (Box 12, Folder 854)
    - Computer Instructions, undated (Box 12, Folder 855)
    - Font Samples, undated (Box 12, Folder 856)
    - Typeface List, undated (Box 12, Folder 857)
    - Issue #1, Mock Up, undated (Box 12, Folder 858)
    - Issue #1, Layout Materials, undated (Box 12, Folder 859)
    - Issue #1, Production Elements, undated (Box 12, Folder 860)
    - Issue #1, MS Envelope w/notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 861)
    - Issue #1, Proofed MS, DeCapite, undated (Box 12, Folder 862)
    - Issue #1, Proofed MS, Godfrey, undated (Box 12, Folder 863)
    - Issue #1, Proofed MS, Hardin, undated (Box 12, Folder 864)
    - Issue #1, Proofed MS, Hell, undated (Box 12, Folder 865)
    - Issue #1, Proofed MS, Mueller, undated (Box 12, Folder 866)
    - Issue #1, Proofed MS, Myles, undated (Box 12, Folder 867)
    - Issue #1, Proofed MS, Wojnarowicz, undated (Box 12, Folder 868)
    - Issue #1, Proofed MS, Zedd, undated (Box 12, Folder 869)
    - Issue #1, Layout, undated (Box 12, Folder 870)
    - Issue #1, 5 ¼ inch Floppy Discs, undated (Box 12, Folder 871)
    - Issue #1, 3 ½ inch disc, undated (Box 12, Folder 872)
    - Issue #1, Cover, undated (Box 13, Folder 873)
    - Issue #1, Proof, undated (Box 13, Folder 874)
    - Issue #1, Final, undated (Box 13, Folder 875)
    - Issue #2, material list, undated (Box 13, Folder 876)
    - Issue #2, Dennis Cooper research, undated (Box 13, Folder 877)
    - Issue #2, Proofed MS, Brown Lee Ann, undated (Box 13, Folder 878)
    - Issue #2, Proofed MS, Burroughs,Williams, undated (Box 13, Folder 879)
    - Issue #2, Proofed MS, Cooper,Dennis, undated (Box 13, Folder 880)
    - Issue #2, Proofed MS, DeCapite,Mike, undated (Box 13, Folder 881)
    - Issue #2, Proofed MS, Dubris,Maggie, undated (Box 13, Folder 882)
    - Issue #2, Proofed MS, Hell,Richard, undated (Box 13, Folder 883)
    - Issue #2, Proofed MS, Kraut,Rochelle, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 884)
    - Issue #2, Production File, Myles,Eileen, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 885)
    - Issue #2 Proofed MS, Patton, Will, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 886)
    - Issue #2 Proofed MS, Russakoff, Molly, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 887)
    - Issue #2 Proofed MS, Timmons, Susie, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 888)
    - Issue #2 Production Materials, Proofs, undated (Box 13, Folder 889)
    - Issue #2 Production Files, Layout, undated (Box 13, Folder 890)
    - Issue #2 Production Files, Discs, undated (Box 13, Folder 891)
    - Issue #2 Production Files, Disc, undated (Box 13, Folder 892)
    - Issue #2 Proof, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 893)
    - Issue #2 CUZ, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 894)
    - Issue #3 Production Files, Zedd, Nick, undated (Box 13, Folder 895)
    - Issue #3 Production Files, envelope for MS, undated (Box 13, Folder 896)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS, Andrews, Bruce, undated (Box 13, Folder 897)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS, Ashbery,John, undated (Box 13, Folder 898)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS, DeCapite, Mike, undated (Box 13, Folder 899)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS, Fagin, Larry, undated (Box 13, Folder 900)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS, Hardin, Terri, undated (Box 13, Folder 901)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS Hell, Richard, undated (Box 13, Folder 902)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS, Hyfill, Mitch, undated (Box 13, Folder 903)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS, Johnson, Janice, undated (Box 13, Folder 904)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS, Lyons, Kim, undated (Box 13, Folder 905)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS, Jerome, undated (Box 13, Folder 906)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS, Trinidad, David, undated (Box 13, Folder 907)
    - Issue #3 Proofed MS, Yan, John, undated (Box 13, Folder 908)
    - Issue #3 Production Files, Photos, Zedd,N, undated (Box 13, Folder 909)
    - Issue #3 Production Files, Proofs, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 910)
    - Issue #3 Production Files, lino proofs, 1989 (Box 13A [flat], Folder 910A)
    - Issue #3 Production Materials, Layout, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 911)
    - Issue #3 Production Files, Sample Issue, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 912)
    - Issue #3 Production Files, Layout, undated (Box 13, Folder 913)
    - Issue #3 Cover, undated (Box 13, Folder 914)
    - Issue #3 Production Files, Proof, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 915)
    - Issue #3 Cuz, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 916)
    - Consignment Slips, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 917)
    - Business Files, CLMP, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 918)
    - Issue #1, Release Party, undated (Box 13, Folder 919)
    - Business Files, Grants, undated (Box 13, Folder 920)
    - Letterhead, undated (Box 13, Folder 921)
  - Subseries Q: Poetry Collections
    Materials relating to Richard Hell's poetry collections, I was a Spiral on the Floor and Across the Years and the Poets' Banquet for the publication of a new issue of CUZ Magazine
    - Invitations, Poet's Banquet, undated (Box 13, Folder 922)
    - Poet's Banquet, Hell, Richard, undated (Box 13, Folder 923)
    - Poet's Banquet, write up, images, undated (Box 13, Folder 924)
    - Press Release, undated (Box 13, Folder 925)
    - Signs, undated (Box 13, Folder 926)
    - Subscription requests, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 927)
    - Business Files, Tax, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 928)
    - Proof, I was a Spiral on the Floor, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 929)
    - Proof, Across the Years, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 930)
  - Subseries R: Artifact: Notebooks from Hell, 1974-80,(1990)
    Materials relating to the publication and publicity of Richard Hell's collection of materials from his journals published by Hanuman Books.
    - Across the Years, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 931)
    - "Fetishistic Souvenirs," Envelope, undated (Box 13, Folder 932)
    - Draft with corrections, undated (Box 13, Folder 933)
    - Unrequited Narcissism, Early draft, undated (Box 13, Folder 934)
    - Unrequited Narcissism, Drafts, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 935)
    - Unrequited Narcissism, Intro, Notebook, undated (Box 13, Folder 936)
    - Unrequited Narcissism, Materials, undated (Box 13, Folder 937)
    - Unrequited Narcissism, Tablet, Intro, undated (Box 13, Folder 938)
    - Unrequited Narcissism, Notepad, undated (Box 13, Folder 939)
    - Incomplete Draft, undated (Box 13, Folder 940)
    - Introduction Drafts, undated (Box 13, Folder 941)
    - Draft, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 942)
    - Draft Publishers Agreement, undated (Box 14, Folder 944)
    - Publication Agreement, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 945)
    - Contract, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 946)
    - Promotional Material, undated (Box 14, Folder 947)
    - Book Party Invitation, undated (Box 14, Folder 948)
    - Artifact, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 949)
    - East Coast Rocker Review, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 950)
    - Press, Spin Mag., 1991 (Box 14, Folder 951)
    - Forced Exposure, review #17, undated (Box 14, Folder 952)
  - Subseries S: Western Love Drive
    Materials relating to the screenplay of the unproduced film, Western Love Drive, written by Richard Hell as commissioned by Kim Massee to be the screenplay version of a story by her.
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 953)
    - Script pages, undated (Box 14, Folder 954)
    - Notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 955)
    - Synopsis, undated (Box 14, Folder 956)
    - Screenplay, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 957)
  - Subseries T: Cookie Mueller Book
    Materials relating to Richard Hell's editing a book as a tribute to Cookie Mueller, the project was never completed.
    - Postcard, undated (Box 14, Folder 958)
    - UK Tax Relief, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 959)
    - Danspace MS,. Inv., undated (Box 14, Folder 960)
    - MS, Notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 961)
    - CL, undated (Box 14, Folder 962)
    - CV, undated (Box 14, Folder 963)
    - Name List, undated (Box 14, Folder 964)
    - Copyright Form, undated (Box 14, Folder 965)
    - Phone Msg, undated (Box 14, Folder 966)
    - High Risk Questionnaire., undated (Box 14, Folder 967)
    - Amy Scholder Corr., undated (Box 14, Folder 968)
    - Cookie Mueller Book, R. Turley, memo, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 969)
    - Rex Fdn, Corr., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 970)
    - Pub. Agreement Drafts, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 971)
    - I.Silverberg Corr., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 972)
    - I. Silverberg, PPOW, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 973)
    - Janice Birney Corr., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 974)
    - I. Silverberg Corr., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 975)
    - Publications Agr., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 976)
    - ChiChi Valenti Corr., 1993 (Box 14, Folder 977)
    - I.Silverberg Cancel.Cont., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 978)
    - Linda Yablonksy,Corr, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 979)
    - Raymond Foye Corr., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 980)
    - Band Corr., undated (Box 14, Folder 981)
  - Subseries U: Dim Stars (1992)
    Materials relating to the production of the album Dim Stars, a collaboration between Richard Hell, Thurston Moore, Steve Shelley and others.
    - Business Corr., 1991 (Box 14, Folder 982)
    - CD Booklet, undated (Box 14, Folder 983)
    - Legal, Memo to Marty, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 984)
    - Lyrics, undated (Box 14, Folder 985)
    - Photos, undated (Box 14, Folder 986)
    - Promo Mat., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 987)
    - R.Hell corr. to NME, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 988)
    - Promo, Rolling Stone, #633, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 989)
    - Promo,Rolling Stone #638, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 990)
    - Promo, Spex #9, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 991)
    - Press, Spin, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 992)
    - Reviews, Press, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 993)
  - Subseries V: The Voidoid
    Materials relating to the publication of Richard Hell's novella, written in the seventies.
    - Box, undated (Box 14, Folder 994)
    - Letter, undated (Box 14, Folder 995)
    - Early Drafts, undated (Box 14, Folder 996)
    - Drafts, undated (Box 14, Folder 997)
    - Cover Design, undated (Box 14, Folder 998)
    - Master, undated (Box 14, Folder 999)
    - Contract Drafts, Corr., 1995 (Box 14, Folder 1000)
    - Editorial Corr., 1994 (Box 14, Folder 1001)
    - Sample Pages, Cover, undated (Box 14, Folder 1002)
    - Proof, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 1003)
    - The Voidoid, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 1004)
  - Subseries W: Theresa Stern Story
    Materials relating to the drafting of the screenplay, shooting and post-production for a film based on the life of Theresa Stern.
    - Script First Draft, undated (Box 14, Folder 1005)
    - Script, MS pgs., undated (Box 14, Folder 1006)
    - Script, First Draft,(1-10), 1987 (Box 14, Folder 1007)
    - Early Frag Draft, (2-10), undated (Box 14, Folder 1008)
    - Early Frag Draft, (1-32), undated (Box 14, Folder 1009)
    - Early Draft Fragment, (10a-10b), undated (Box 14, Folder 1010)
    - Early Draft Fragment (14-18), undated (Box 14, Folder 1011)
    - Early Draft Fragment(18-68), undated (Box 14, Folder 1012)
    - Early Draft Fragment(46-68), undated (Box 14, Folder 1013)
    - Early Draft Fragment, undated (Box 14, Folder 1014)
    - Deletions, undated (Box 14, Folder 1015)
    - MS, Treatment, undated (Box 14, Folder 1016)
    - Treatment, undated (Box 14, Folder 1017)
    - Revised Draft,(1-11), undated (Box 14, Folder 1018)
    - Revised Draft, part 2, undated (Box 14, Folder 1019)
    - Revised Draft, part 3, undated (Box 14, Folder 1020)
    - Press, Interview, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 1021)
    - Screenplay, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1022)
    - Script, William Morris Ag., 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1023)
    - Treatment, William Morris Ag, undated (Box 14, Folder 1024)
    - Scene Outline, undated (Box 14, Folder 1025)
    - Press, Doris Kornish, undated (Box 14, Folder 1026)
    - Breathing Films L.H. design, undated (Box 14, Folder 1027)
    - Master Script and notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 1028)
    - Screenplay, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1029)
    - Screenplay, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1030)
    - Ltd. Partnership Agreement, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1031)
    - Letter of Agreement, Amos Poe, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1032)
    - Corr., Tom Verlaine, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 1033)
    - Scene breakdown, undated (Box 14, Folder 1034)
    - Budget, undated (Box 15, Folder 1035)
    - Funding Research, undated (Box 15, Folder 1036)
    - AFI Grant App., 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1037)
    - NEA Grant App., 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1038)
    - Pub., NY Observor, undated (Box 15, Folder 1039)
    - Richard Hell resume, undated (Box 15, Folder 1040)
    - Materials for Grant App., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1041)
    - Annotated pol. script, undated (Box 15, Folder 1042)
    - Script Log, undated (Box 15, Folder 1043)
    - Invoices, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1044)
    - Receipts,Invoices, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1045)
    - Workers Comp. Ins., 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1046)
    - Resources, Crew, undated (Box 15, Folder 1047)
    - Valk, Kate, Headshots, undated (Box 15, Folder 1048)
    - Cast and Crew List, undated (Box 15, Folder 1049)
    - General Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 1050)
    - Production Binder, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1051)
    - Storyboard, undated (Box 15, Folder 1052)
    - Shooting Schedules, undated (Box 15, Folder 1053)
    - Shot List, undated (Box 15, Folder 1054)
    - Shot List, scene 9, undated (Box 15, Folder 1055)
    - Wanna Go Out?, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1056)
    - Photograph, undated (Box 15, Folder 1057)
    - Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 1058)
    - Notes,theme,plot,etc., undated (Box 15, Folder 1059)
    - Misc.Shooting, Plays, Script, undated (Box 15, Folder 1060)
    - Wig Catalog, undated (Box 15, Folder 1061)
    - Notes on reel 1,2,3, undated (Box 15, Folder 1062)
    - Edge Nos., Code Nos., undated (Box 15, Folder 1063)
    - Postproduction Notes,sound, undated (Box 15, Folder 1064)
    - Postproduction Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 1065)
    - Postproduction Receipts, undated (Box 15, Folder 1066)
    - Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 1067)
    - Wild Sound List, undated (Box 15, Folder 1068)
    - Reading, Corr.,K.Cartlidge., undated (Box 15, Folder 1069)
    - Screenplay,reading version, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1070)
    - MS Page, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1071)
    - Reading at Nuyorican, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1072)
    - Credits for Balthazar Screening, undated (Box 15, Folder 1073)
    - Festival Balthazar, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 1074)
    - Printed Material, Richard Hell Theresa Stern, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 1075)
    - Misc.Material, "Danielle", undated (Box 15, Folder 1076)
    - Misc. Materials, undated (Box 15, Folder 1077)
  - Subseries X: Go Now (1996)
    Manuscript drafts of and materials relating to the publication of Richard Hell's novel, published by Scribner's.
    - materials-photocopies of roadtrip, undated (Box 15, Folder 1078)
    - Folder for early drafts, undated (Box 15, Folder 1079)
    - Fresh + Firm treatment, undated (Box 15, Folder 1080)
    - MS Part I (1-4), undated (Box 15, Folder 1081)
    - MS Ch. 2 (2 versions), undated (Box 15, Folder 1082)
    - MS, Ch.2, Deleted Pages, undated (Box 15, Folder 1083)
    - Drafts, Chapt.2,Early Version, undated (Box 15, Folder 1084)
    - Opening, (versions), undated (Box 15, Folder 1085)
    - Ch.1, Typescript, undated (Box 15, Folder 1086)
    - Ch.1-2,Typescript, undated (Box 15, Folder 1087)
    - Draft, Ch.1-2, undated (Box 15, Folder 1088)
    - Draft, Ch.. 1-2 w/corrections, undated (Box 15, Folder 1089)
    - Drafts,Ch.3,Typescript, undated (Box 15, Folder 1090)
    - Drafts, Ch. 3, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1091)
    - Draft, Ch. 4, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1092)
    - Draft Ch.1-5, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1093)
    - Draft,Ch.5, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1094)
    - Drafts Ch.6, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1095)
    - Draft Ch.1-2, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1096)
    - Draft, Ch. 3-4, undated (Box 15, Folder 1097)
    - Draft, Ch.5-7, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1098)
    - Draft, Ch.1-9, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 1099)
    - Excerpts,Page Proofs,Tales of LES, undated (Box 15, Folder 1100)
    - Flap Copy Drafts, undated (Box 15, Folder 1101)
    - Draft, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1102)
    - Master, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1103)
    - Draft With Corrections, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1104)
    - Submission letter/list of Pub., 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1105)
    - Rejection Letters, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1106)
    - Corr. Harper Collins, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1107)
    - Draft with Editors comments, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1108)
    - Draft, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 1109)
    - Copyedited MS, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1110)
    - Draft with Revisions, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1111)
    - Corrected Page Proofs, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1112)
    - Proofer's Comments/Style Sheet, undated (Box 16, Folder 1113)
    - Corrected Pub.Info.Pg., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1114)
    - Author Photo, Photographer: Melanie Weiner, undated (Box 16, Folder 1115)
    - Page Design, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1116)
    - Cover Artifact, (unused), undated (Box 16, Folder 1117)
    - Nan Goldin Photo, Price Structure, undated (Box 16, Folder 1118)
    - Cover art, US, undated (Box 16, Folder 1119)
    - Press GQ, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1120)
    - Corr. re: UK cover design, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1121)
    - Road Trip photos for UK cover, undated (Box 16, Folder 1122)
    - Cover Art, UK, undated (Box 16, Folder 1123)
    - UK Contract and Corr., 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1124)
    - US, Proof, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1125)
    - Scribners Pub.Agreement, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1126)
    - Letters to Reviewers (Scribners), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1127)
    - Scribners Press Release, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1128)
    - Reception invitation, undated (Box 16, Folder 1129)
    - Fourth Estate Catalog, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1130)
    - UK Proof, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1131)
    - Scribners Catalog, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1132)
    - Promo Materials,Scribner Mag., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1133)
    - UK Publicity, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1134)
    - Promotions,Publicity Sched., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1135)
    - UK Publicity Sched., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1136)
    - Publicity, Summerstage Cont., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1137)
    - Paper, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1138)
    - Alternative Press, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1139)
    - Press ID, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1140)
    - Press - Prime, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1141)
    - TimeOut NY,"Hell on Wheels", 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1142)
    - The List, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1143)
    - Times Literary Supp., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1144)
    - Highland News Group, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1145)
    - Scotland on Sunday, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1146)
    - City Life, Manchester UK, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1147)
    - Press, Dazed and Confused #22, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1148)
    - Paint it Red, Newcastle UK, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1149)
    - Record Collection, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1150)
    - Glasgow Herald, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1151)
    - New Statement & Society, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1152)
    - The Nation "Hell is Other People", 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1153)
    - Glasgow Herald, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1154)
    - New York "To Hell and Back", 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1155)
    - Evening Standard, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1156)
    - Esquire (UK)Author's Choice, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1157)
    - Q #119"To Hell in a Hardback", 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1158)
    - Punter, What's on in Sussex, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1159)
    - Yorkshire Evening Post, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1160)
    - Hot Press, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1161)
    - USA Today, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1162)
    - Orlando Centennial, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1163)
    - The Lock Magazine, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1164)
    - Mojo, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1165)
    - Previews, LA Times, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1166)
    - High Times #255, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1167)
    - Hanatsubaki, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1168)
    - Technikart, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1169)
    - Rage #44, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 1170)
    - The Briefundated (Box 16, Folder 1171)
    - The Guardian, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1172)
    - San Jose Mercury News, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1173)
    - Vanidad, undated (Box 16, Folder 1174)
    - Venue, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1175)
    - Press Clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 1176)
    - Promotion Blurbs, undated (Box 16, Folder 1177)
    - Trade Paperback Press release, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 1178)
    - FanMail, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1179)
    - Correspondence, Ellen, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1180)
    - Correspondence, Lord Durmond, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1181)
    - Correspondence, Publishers, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1182)
    - Correspondence, Stone,Laurie, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1183)
    - Correspondence, University New Orleans, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1184)
    - Correspondence, Barnes & Nobles, D.Williams, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1185)
    - Correspondence Partial Name, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1186)